Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Public Relations, 1956-2012
  - Subseries 1.3: District Mailers, 1971-2007
    - 37th Congressional District, 1981 August (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1981 September (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1981 November (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 January (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 February (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 June (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 July (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 August (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - 37th Congressional District, 1982 September (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1983 March (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - District Lists by Zipcode, 1983 March (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1983 June (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1983 September (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1983 November (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1983 December (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1984 January (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1984 February (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1984 June (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - 35th Congressional District, 1984 August (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - 40th Congressional District, 1993 December (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Jerry Lewis Form Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jerry Lewis Form Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 41st Congressional District, 2007 December (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Form Letters to Constituents, 2004-2011 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Mailers and Franking, 1985-1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Mailers and Franking, 1985-1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Mailer, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Mailer, July 2008 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Mailer, 2010 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.4: Correspondence, 1969-2012
    This subseries contains a wide sampling of the correspondence that passed through Lewis's Assembly and congressional offices, from as early as 1973 to the end of his career in 2012. The largest categories of correspondence are: letters and invitations sent from the White House, thank-you notes sent from and to Congressman Lewis, copies of letters written jointly with other members of Congress and signed by Lewis, and interoffice memoranda written by members of Lewis's staff. The most distinctive documents in this subseries are Lewis's collection of presidential inauguration invitations and supporting documents such as menus and parking passes.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically by subject.
    - Bipartisan Congressional Retreat, 1996-1998 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Birthday Messages and Condolences, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Birthday Messages and Condolences, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Brazil: Invitation, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - CA Assembly Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - CA Assembly: Capital Report, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - CA Assembly: Radio Scripts, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - California Delegation Letters, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Carl Kime, House Fellows Program, 2006-2007 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of Election, 1976-2010 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Community Forum Notices, 1987, 1992, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Congratulation Letters to Jerry Lewis, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Congratulation Letters to Jerry Lewis on His Chairmanship, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Delegation to Livingston, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Record Remarks, 1990-1992 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Coro Foundation, 1984-1992 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Coro Foundation, 1984-1988 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Coro Foundation, Program Description, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1980, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1991, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 2003-2007 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 2009-2012 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Department of Education Memos, 2006-2007 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Department of Justice, OIG Audit of NDAA, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1983-1989 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - George Herbert Walker Bush, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Governor Ronald Reagan, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Guide to 98th Congress, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - House That Congress Built, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Iaoccca Biography, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Invitation Acceptance and Rejection, 1976-1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Jerry Lewis, Comedian, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Jerry Lewis Caricature, Other Assorted Oversized Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1999-2001 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1999-2009 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 1999-2009 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Jerry Lewis Signed Letters, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Judicial Appointments, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Lending Jerry Lewis's Name, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Lending Jerry Lewis's Name, 1997-1998 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Loma Linda Children's Hospital Gala, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Medicare Mailer, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Mojave Water Agency Tribute to Jerry Lewis, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Office Memoranda, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Office Memoranda, 2004, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Office Memoranda: Abigail Emerson, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Office Memoranda: Al Zane, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Office Memoranda: Bob Okun, 1985? (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Office Memoranda: Brian Lockwood, 1980, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Office Memoranda:Darin LaHood, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Office Memoranda: Dave Ramey, 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Office Memoranda: David Les Strang, 1988, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Office Memoranda: Doc Syers, 1988-1994 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Office Memoranda: Ed Slevin, 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Office Memoranda: Flint Lewis Memos, 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Office Memoranda: Frank Gregorsky, 1984-1990 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Office Memoranda: Frank Gregorsky, 1984-1990 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Office Memoranda: Frank Gregorsky, 1986-1991 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Office Memoranda: Frank Gregorsky, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Office Memoranda: Frank Gregorsky, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Office Memoranda: Kevin Huiskes, 1981-1983, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Office Memoranda: Jeff Shockey, 1992-1995 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Office Memoranda: Policy, 1980-1995 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Office Memoranda: Republican Conference Budget, 1987-1991 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Recommendation Letters, 1975-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Recommendation Letters, 2006-2007 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Richard Nixon, 1978, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Sample Letters to and from Constituents, 1982-1991 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Senator Alan Cranston, Press Releases, 1982-1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - September 11 Condolences, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Telegrams to Jerry Lewis, 1974-1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Thank-You Letters from Jerry Lewis, 1976-1992 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Thank-You Letters, 1980-1988 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Thank-You Letters, 1988-2012 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Thank-You Letters, 1996-2012 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Thank-You Letters, 2003-2008 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Thank-You Letters, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - White House Conference on Small Business, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - White House Notes, 1984-1991 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - White House Notes, 1984-1991 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - White House Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - White House Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - White House Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - White House Notes, 1987-2008 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - White House Notes, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - White House Notes, 2001-2003 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - William Jefferson Clinton, 1993-2000 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 1.5: Travel, Events, and Speeches, 1956-2012
    This subseries is fairly evenly divided between travel documentation and scripts of speeches given by Congressman Lewis at various domestic events. There are itineraries, maps, receipts, and correspondence related to both international and domestic travel. The international travel was mostly taken in the context of official congressional delegations, although there are a number of trips that Lewis took alone—for example, when he attended a six-week Spanish immersion program in Mexico in 1998. Also included in this section are a variety of awards and certificates presented to Lewis during his years in the California Assembly and Congress.
    - Awards, Certificates Given to Jerry Lewis, 1988-2009 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Awards, Letters, Various, 1980-1989, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Awards and Certificates for Jerry Lewis, 1977, 1988-2008 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Awards and Certificates for Jerry Lewis, 1988-2009 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Bahrain, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Jordan, Belgium: Congressional Delegation, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Bosnia: Congressional Delegation, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - California, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - California, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - California, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - California, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - California State Assembly Travel Documents, 1970-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Committee Travel, 1996-2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Credit Crunch Conference, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - District of Colombia: Lewis Center Visit, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - District Office Schedules, 1989-1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - District Office Schedules, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - District Office Schedules, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - District Office Schedules, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - District Office Schedules, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - District Office Schedules, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - District Office Schedules, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Egypt: Maryut Project Coordination Meeting, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - El Salvador: Congressional Delegation, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Event Programs, 2001, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - FDR Memorial Dedication, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Floor Remarks, Various Subjects, 1992, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - France: Congressional Delegation, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - France, Bosnia, Italy, Portugal: Congressional Delegation, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - France, Bosnia, Italy, Portugal: Congressional Delegation, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Full Committee Chairman Notes, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Hawaii: Congressional Delegation, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Inauguration, Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - India: Project India, 1965-1966, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - India: Project India, 1956-1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - India: Project India, 1956-1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - India: Project India Reunion, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Ireland, UK, France: Congressional Delegation, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Ireland: Congressional Delegation, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Ireland, Italy, Czech Republic, Spain: Congressional Delegation, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Italy, Macedonia, Kosovo, Turkey, Germany: Congressional Delegation, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Italy, Macedonia, Kosovo, Turkey, Germany: Congressional Delegation, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Italy: Congressional Delegation, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Jerry Lewis Portrait Unveiling, 2009 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Jerry Lewis Portrait Unveiling, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Loma Linda University, Proton Treatment Center Anniversary, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Mexico, 1989-1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Mexico: Immersive Spanish Class, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - New Mexico, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nicaragua, El Salvador, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Northern Marianas Islands, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Poland, Portugal, UK: Congressional Delegation, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Presidential Inaugurations, 1985, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Presidential Inaugurations, 2005, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Pope John Paul II Speech, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Republican Luau, Contemporary Club Luncheon, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Russia: Space Station, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Speeches, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Speeches: CA Assembly Speaker, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Speeches: Governor Jerry Brown, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Speeches: Jerry Lewis, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Speeches: Jerry Lewis, 1970-1973, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Speeches: Jerry Lewis, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Speeches: Jerry Lewis, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Speeches: Jerry Lewis, 1972-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Speeches: Governor Ronald Reagan, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Speeches: Governor Ronald Reagan, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Speeches: Governor Ronald Reagan, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Speeches: Governor Ronald Reagan, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Speeches: Various, 1982, 1990-1991, 2012 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Various, 1991-1994 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Speeches: Various, 1991-1994 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Taiwan, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Tele Town Hall Meeting Notes, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Tele Town Hall Meeting Talking Points, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Tele Town Hall Meeting Talking Points, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Turkey, Greece, Germany, Luxembourg, Italy, Gibraltar: Congressional Delegation, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - UCLA, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - UCLA Commencement, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - US Congress: Community Forum Mailings, 1979-1983 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - US Virgin Islands: Congressional Delegation, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - US Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico: Congressional Delegation, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Various Travel Receipts, 1975-1978 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Washington, Alaska, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - White House, Congressional Invitations, 1989-2009 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Election Campaigns, 1968-2010
  This series contains the records Jerry Lewis and his staff kept regarding his election campaigns, starting with his first campaign for California State Assembly in 1968 and ending with his second to last campaign for Congress in 2008. For each campaign, Lewis kept detailed financial reports, records of his fundraising events, samples of his advertising and distribution materials, copies of his correspondence, data on his constituency, research on his campaign opponents, and official documentation required by the State of California for all candidates. This series also includes files on other election campaigns which Lewis either researched as part of his own campaign strategy or endorsed, including Ronald Reagan's failed campaign for the presidency in 1977.
  - Subseries 2.1: California State Assembly, 1968-1978
    This subseries, which spans from 1968 to 1978, includes the files Lewis and his staff maintained for the five election cycles Lewis entered during his ten-year tenure in the California State Assembly. Within these campaign records are detailed financial reports, including state-mandated Campaign Statements, invitations, guest lists, and seating arrangements for campaign fundraisers, and statistical and demographic research conducted on Lewis's constituency. Of special interest to researchers will be the scrapbook Lewis created to commemorate his 1968 run for State Assembly, which includes press clippings, bumper stickers, and mailers from his first assembly campaign. Researchers may also be interested in the collection of brief candidate biographies Lewis created for press purposes during his Assembly campaigns, in which changes to his credentials and the directions of his campaigns might be observed.
    - 1968 Election: Political Survey of 73rd Assembly District, 1968 October 16-19 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Scrapbook, 1969-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1972 Election: Distribution Materials, circa 1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions Thank-you Letters, 1973 September-1974 September (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - 1972 Election: Finances: Campaign Statements, 1972 June-1975 December (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - 1974 Election: Fundraiser Event: Sloan, James; Redlands, California, 1974 November 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 1976 Election: Democrats for Jerry Lewis Write-in Campaign, 1976 April-October (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 1976 Election: Demographic and Statistical Data, San Bernardino Older Residents, 1976 March (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - 1976 Election: Finances: Audit Report, Franchise Tax Board, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - 1976 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions Thank-you Letter, 1976 May 7 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - 1976 Election: Finances: Campaign Statements, 1976 May-December (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - 1976 Election: Fundraiser Event: Chino, California, 1976 December 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 1976 Election: Fundraiser Event: Redlands, California, 1976 April 23 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - 1976 Election: Fundraiser Event: Riverside, California, 1976 February 24 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - 1976 Election: Primary Election Direct Data, 1976 June 8 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - 1978 Election: Candidates' Materials (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Biographies of Jerry Lewis for Assembly Campaigns, 1968-1978 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Subseries 2.2: California State Senate, 1973-1976
    This subseries contains all files related to Jerry Lewis's failed campaign for the California State Senate in 1974. Included in these records are state-mandated financial campaign statements, correspondence between Lewis and his campaign contributors, distribution materials for voters, and transcripts of local radio advertisements. Of special interest to researchers may be the documentation of campaign expenses, which detail the local businesses, volunteers, and staff involved in this election.
    - 1974 Election: Advertisements: Radio, 1973 December-1974 May (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - 1974 Election: Distribution Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Audit Report, Franchise Tax Board, 1976 December 17 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions, 1973 November-1974 January (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions Thank-you Letters, 1974 February 26-28 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions Thank-you Letters, 1975 October (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Contributions Thank-you Letters, Blank Form, 1974 March 6 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Statements, Lewis for Senate Committee, 1973 November-December (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Statements, Lewis for Senate Committee, 1974 January-October (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Campaign Statements, Lewis for Senate Committee, 1975 January-1976 July (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Expenses (1 of 2), 1973 October-1974 August (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - 1974 Election: Finances: Expenses (2 of 2), 1973 October-1974 August (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 1974 Election: Identification Number, Lewis for Senate Committee, 1974 March 21 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1974 Election: Volunteers for Campaign, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.3: United States Congress, 1970-2010
    Jerry Lewis first ran for congress in 1978 and continued to run and be elected until his retirement in 2012, a tenure of almost thirty-five years. During his participation in the sixteen elections entered into for the United States House of Representatives, he kept detailed records of his campaigns. These include financial records, such as correspondence related to campaign contributions, official campaign statements, and budgets; fundraising information, such as invitations, guest lists, contribution information, and seating charts; and advertising and publicizing materials, such as television advertisement scripts, bumper stickers, campaign buttons, and mailers.
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Newspaper, 1978 October (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Outdoor Permit, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Poster, Handmade, circa 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Posters, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Radio, 1978 February-June (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 1978 Election: Advertisements: Television, 1978 April-September (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 1978 Election: Biographies of Jerry Lewis, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 1978 Election: Campaign Associates Catalogue, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 1978 Election: Campaign Calendar, 1978 July-November (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - 1978 Election: Campaign Opponents: Advertisements, Letters, Mailers (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 1978 Election: Campaign Strategy Outline by Kerry Haynes, circa 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 1978 Election: Campaign Supplies Companies, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 1978 Election: Candidacy Announcement: Press Statements, Press Clippings, 1978 February-October (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 1978 Election: Candidates, Certified Lists by Secretary of State, 1978 June 6 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 1978 Election: Distribution Materials: Drafts, Photographs, Sketches, circa 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 1978 Election: Distribution Materials: Flyers and Mailers, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 1978 Election: Election Poster, UCLA Poster (Oversized), 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 1978 Election: Endorsements of Lewis, 1978 February-June (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 1978 Election: Endorsements of Lewis: Maddy, Ken: Mailing List, 1978 October 18 (Box 16, Folder 19)